[{
"question": "If Sape Chicago had one more floor, what would you put there?", 
"answers": ["Games", "Sports or fitness equipment", "More meeting rooms", "Sleeping space", "Lounge", "Privacy", "Bar", "Playground"],
"points": [21, 17, 16, 16, 8, 8, 7, 7]
},
{
"question": "Where do you want the next office holiday party to be?", 
"answers": ["Hotel/hotel bar", "Somewhere with a view", "Somewhere warm", "On a boat", "Museum or park space", "Somewhere cheap", "Brewery", "Somewhere in Europe"],
"points": [19, 19, 17, 15, 10, 8, 6, 6]
},
{
"question": "What’s your favorite lunch spot near the office?", 
"answers": ["Chasement", "Hannah’s Bretzel", "Pret", "Benjyehuda", "Chipotle", "Oasis Café", "Saucy Porka"],
"points": [35, 16, 16, 10, 9, 7, 7]
},
{
"question": "Name a personality trait you hope people mention when talking about you", 
"answers": ["Kind", "Friendly", "Funny", "Honest", "Nice", "Awesome", "Smart", "Trustworthy"],
"points": [22, 15, 15, 12, 12, 8, 8, 8]
},
{
"question": "What’s your favorite board game?", 
"answers": ["Monopoly", "Scrabble", "Risk", "Clue", "Trivial Pursuit", "Settlers of Catan", "Cards Against Humanity", "Scattergories"],
"points": [26, 20, 15, 13, 7, 7, 7, 5]
},
{
"question": "What Sapient office would you most like to visit?",
"answers": ["London", "LA/Santa Monica", "Miami", "Sydney", "Bangalore", "NYC", "Singapore"],
"points": [24, 17, 17, 16, 10, 8, 8]	
},
{
"question": "What snack do you always keep at your desk?",
"answers": ["Chocolate", "Almonds", "Candy", "Fruit", "Booze", "Cookies", "Food Bar"],
"points": [20, 20, 15, 15, 11, 10, 9]	
},
{
"question": "What is one thing you avoid when taking public transit?",
"answers": ["People", "Strange Smells", "Touching Things", "Wet/Sticky Seats", "Urine", "Eye Contact", "Bums", "Standing"],
"points": [27, 20, 17, 8, 7, 7, 7, 7]
},
{
"question": "What is the best neighborhood in Chicago?",
"answers": ["Wicker Park", "Logan Square", "Lincoln Park", "River North", "Old Town", "Lakeview", "West Loop", "Andersonville"],
"points": [21, 19, 17, 15, 15, 13]
},
{
"question": "What's your one word reaction to the words 'polar vortex'?",
"answers": ["F**k/Other Expletives", "Brrr", "Cold", "Ugh", "Chicago", "No", "Freezing"],
"points": [35, 20, 11, 11, 9, 7, 7]
},
{
"question": "What's the first app you use when you wake up?",
"answers": ["Email", "Weather", "News/Magazine/ESPN", "Instagram", "Facebook", "Reddit", "Alarm"],
"points": [28, 19, 17, 13, 13, 6, 4]
},
{
"question": "Name the chore that you dread the most",
"answers": ["Laundry", "Dishes", "Cleaning Bathroom", "Taking out the Trash", "Work Duties", "Cleauygtning Baby/Cat Poop"],
"points": [28, 26, 17, 10, 10, 9]
},
{
"question": "What's the worst thing to realize that you left home without?",
"answers": ["Phone","Keys","Wallet", "Pants", "Computer", "CTA/Transit Pass", "Headphones", "Deodorant"],
"points": [42, 14, 12, 8, 8, 6, 5, 5]
},
{	
"question": "What's your favorite playground equipment?",
"answers": ["Swing", "Monkey Bars", "Slide", "Merry-go-round", "A Ball"],
"points": [56, 17, 16, 5, 5]
}]